TYO PRATAMA PRIYANTO PUTRA

github.com/tyoprataama | tyoprataama004@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/tyo-pratama/

Kediri, East Java

My name is Tyo Pratama Priyanto Putra. I am a self-taught programmer, especially in front-end engineering. I am creative and capable of collaborate effectively with multidisciplinary teams to achieve common goals. Through my experiences, manage to developed a strong foundation skillset related to product lifecycle management, project management, scrum, user experience, analytical and problem solving. I am motivated to apply my skills and knowledge to help drive product innovation and growth in a fast- paced and exciting environment.

Work Experiences

BTPN Syariah - Indonesia

Apr 2023 - May 2023

Fullstack Developer Project Based Intern

- Learn about Vue JS as main frontend framework at the company.
- Learn about Java and Golang and implementation into backend applications.
- · Learn about database SQL and simple query.
- Building project API for final exercise.

SoftwareSeni - Indonesia Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

Frontend Developer Intern

- Learn about JavaScript and implementation into React framework.
- Building and develop resource management website using React TypeScript and Material UI for the CSS.
- · Learn about Next JS.
- Worked in SCRUM environment and followed the SCRUM cycles such as sprint planning, daily standup, sprint review and sprint retrospective.

Digital Talent Scholarship - Indonesia

May 2022 - Jun 2022

Data Engineer

- · Learn about Python for basic data engineer.
- · Learn about SQL database.
- Develop data manipulation with pandas library.
- · Building data project with pandas library.

Digital Talent Scholarship - Indonesia

Mar 2022 - May 2022

Backend Developer

- · Learn about JavaScript and implementation into back-end applications.
- · Building basic of RESTful API from HTTP servers and routing.
- Learn about back-end applications framework (Hapi JS).
- Building first cloud architecture on AWS.
- · Learn about database (PostgreSQL) and database query.

Education Level

IAIN Kediri - Indonesia Aug 2019 - May 2023

Bachelor Degree in Sharia Economy, 3.58/4.00

· Relevant Coursework: Business Accounting, Data Analysis for Business

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Achievements (2021): Inovation Web, Mobile-App and Android Issued by Universitas Sebelas Maret 1st place in category "Post-Pandemic Economic Improvement".
- · Skills: In-depth knowledge of Fullstack Engineering especially using JavaScript Programming Language.